stratics.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Stratics Community Forums

__

**Stratics Community Forums**

[__](https://stratics.com/) Help >

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Privacy Policy applies to Stratics.com (including subdomains and redirects) and its parent company, Gamer's Gambit, LLC., collectively referred to as "Gamer's Gambit, LLC." in this document, and governs data collection and usage. By using the Gamer's Gambit, LLC. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age and gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Gamer's Gambit, LLC.. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Gamer's Gambit, LLC. website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Gamer's Gambit, LLC.'s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Gamer's Gambit, LLC. so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Gamer's Gambit, LLC. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Gamer's Gambit, LLC. website(s).

## Use of your Personal Information

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Gamer's Gambit, LLC. and its affiliates. Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Gamer's Gambit, LLC., and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Gamer's Gambit, LLC., in order to determine what Gamer's Gambit, LLC. services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Gamer's Gambit, LLC. to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Gamer's Gambit, LLC. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Gamer's Gambit, LLC.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Gamer's Gambit, LLC., or the public.

## Use of Cookies

The Gamer's Gambit, LLC. website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a uniquely assigned text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Gamer's Gambit, LLC. pages, or register with Gamer's Gambit, LLC. site or services, a cookie helps Gamer's Gambit, LLC. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Gamer's Gambit, LLC. website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Gamer's Gambit, LLC. features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Gamer's Gambit, LLC. services or websites you visit.

## Security of your Personal Information

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Gamer's Gambit, LLC. uses certain programs and services, which may change or be updated from time to time. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

## Children Under Thirteen

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

## Disconnecting your Gamer's Gambit, LLC. Account from Third Party Websites

You may be able to connect your Gamer's Gambit, LLC. account to third party accounts, such as social media platforms like Facebook or Twitter. BY CONNECTING YOUR Gamer's Gambit, LLC. ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES), INCLUDING TO THE FULL EXTENT OF BOTH Gamer's Gambit, LLC.'S PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY PRIVACY POLICY(S) APPLICABLE TO THE THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT. IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time by visiting your account page. Users may also contact Gamer's Gambit, LLC. via email or website personal message for technical support in disconnecting their account.

## Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

Users may opt-out of receiving some routine communications from Gamer's Gambit, LLC. by contacting us here, or adjusting your personal profile settings on the Site:  
Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## Changes to this Statement

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. will, from time to time and in its sole discretion, update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Gamer's Gambit, LLC. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Gamer's Gambit, LLC. is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Gamer's Gambit, LLC. welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. For any questions, please contact Gamer's Gambit, LLC. at:  
Email Address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  

### Effective as of March 28, 2016

__

**Stratics Community Forums**

[__](https://stratics.com/) Help >
